Astronaut Frank Rubiales has returned to Earth after 371 days in space.
宇航员弗兰克·鲁比亚莱斯在太空停留371天后返回地球。
It was only supposed to be 180, but a technical fault stopped him from returning as planned.
原本计划只停留180天，但一次技术故障使他无法按计划返回。
Unlucky for him, but very lucky for scientists who want to see what effects spending an extended time in space has on the human body.
对他来说是不幸，但对科学家来说却非常幸运，他们想了解在太空度过更长时间对人体有何影响。
Being in space can affect both physical and mental health.
身处太空会影响身心健康。
Weightlessness caused by a lack of gravity can lead to a loss of bone and muscle mass.
失重状态会导致骨量和肌肉量的流失。
Astronauts are recommended 150 minutes of exercise per day to counteract this.
建议宇航员每天锻炼150分钟来抵消这种影响。
Also, space traveller's eyes can be affected by the way that fluids act in zero-gravity.
此外，太空旅行者的眼睛也会受到液体在零重力下行为方式的影响。
Outside the protection of the Earth's atmosphere, astronauts are exposed to much higher levels and different forms of solar radiation.
在地球大气层的保护之外，宇航员会暴露于更高强度和不同形式的太阳辐射下。
This can potentially cause long-term health problems, such as cancer.
这有可能会导致长期健康问题，例如癌症。
It's not just physical health that is affected by being in space.
受到太空影响的不仅仅是身体健康。
Our mental health can be damaged if we don't get enough sleep.
如果睡眠不足，我们的心理健康也会受损。
On earth, our bodies respond through circadian rhythms to the Sun rising and setting to help us sleep, but astronauts on board the International Space Station see 16 sunsets and sunrises every day.
在地球上，我们的身体通过生物钟节律对日出和日落做出反应来帮助我们睡眠，但国际空间站上的宇航员每天会看到16次日落和日出。
This means that avoiding sleep deprivation is a challenge.
这意味着避免睡眠不足是一项挑战。
Isolation, and spending all your time with a small group of people can also affect mental health.
与世隔绝以及与一小群人共度所有时光也会影响心理健康。
Along with isolation, is the pressure that comes from being constantly monitored by experts back on Earth.
与隔绝相伴的，还有来自被地球专家持续监控的压力。
With possible future missions to Mars predicted to last three years, tensions within the crew could become heightened.
鉴于未来可能前往火星的任务预计将持续三年，机组人员内部的紧张关系可能会加剧。
Astronaut Harry Hartfield reports an example of this where a colleague threatened to open the airlock and drain the oxygen from the spacecraft.
宇航员哈里·哈特菲尔德报告了一个例子，一名同事威胁要打开气闸舱，排空飞船中的氧气。
Developing new techniques and technology to support astronauts' health will enable more ambitious future missions.
开发支持宇航员健康的新技术和新科技将使未来更雄心勃勃的任务成为可能。
It can also help those of us who are staying on Earth.
它也能帮助我们这些留在地球上的人。
The Canadian Space Agency is using its expertise to improve health care for people living in remote regions.
加拿大航天局正利用其专业知识来改善偏远地区居民的医疗保健。
The technology that supports robots used in space is now being used in surgery in normal hospitals, while pressure suits are being used to treat post-pregnancy complications.
用于支持太空机器人的技术现在正被用于普通医院的外科手术中，而压力服则被用来治疗产后并发症。